<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Breathe Safari]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Breathe Safari]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/breathe-safari/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 17:24:44 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/breathe-safari/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>BOOK IN TO CONNECT 1 CONTACT US ​</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/breathe-safari/book-in-to-connect-1-contact-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">41e09755-013e-4d0e-bcce-81c38652a6e4</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 17:24:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>In the hustle and bustle of life today, we often forget to just stop… look around us… listen… and breeeeathe! Juggling busy schedules and constant multi-tasking, it’s not easy to take time out and we can become disconnected from our true self, succumbing to the hectic pace like robot minions. BREATHE SAFARI offers a range of holistic health retreats and wellness workshops to rejuvenate the body, revitalise the mind, and re-energise the soul. Whether it’s for a half-day, overnight or weekend, BREATHE SAFARI has created something to suit everyone. Our retreats use restorative practices like yoga, meditation, music, sound healing, fun engaging activities, complemented by wholesome vegetarian food to nourish a reconnection deep within you, in turn transforming the relationships you have with those around you. BREATHE SAFARI workshops help you to rediscover a sense of purpose and clarity in your life, rekindle a sense of community and contribution, explore creativity, embrace gratitude, and encourage the gift of sharing. We aim to nurture your inner strength, so you can break through limitations, and be your best self living your best life.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/breathe-safari/in-the-hustle-and-bustle-of-life-today-we-often-forget-to-j/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c808f503-7b62-4aaa-80ba-849bd106befb</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 17:23:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>WELLNESS EVENTS</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/breathe-safari/wellness-events/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f6535fba-6ca2-4aef-bab4-fde88ba71883</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2016 13:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>